I
Face we borrowed in
Stranger where my own every whisper found a hungry crowd
Every spot became a flame. They say they know what's in my heart like they live
Love isn't the best place to stalk a lover, so the gym is where I go
That is where I spy on you in your box, so pretend I box or sew
Got a weird obsession with the shape of your body, this creepy song is all about that
Make your hands close to the shape of your yes or 10th throat
And the shape of your mouth and I'll sing it like what size are your boxing gloves
Show me your handshake
Hold on, what excuse me?
Come on now, just let me see
I may be crazy, don't be
Say boy
is messed up don't touch my waist why are you measuring me because i look your body um omg you are
this time it gets real fattest and your butt's running bomb last night i was in your this red
rough so i think you're out of shape by your boobs can i measure your insides so let us see your
body watching from the distance so you wouldn't see me it was like we were on our second date
I watched for hours and hours even when you took a shower making my topics of all of your shapes
I lived a note in your lockers and your buddy Stalker was both getting naked, what do you say?
And now you're singing like...
Weirdo, do you just come to the...
Goddamn, it's not my showroom
Yes, of course I box
Okay, then prove it, throw out, check at me
Can I first measure your feet?
Wait, hold on, I've got my panties
Never been locked up
In that ring with you
You're wearing all your shapes with this look
Here's your shades I got just for you
One of us bare tooth
It's coffee but I forgot my phone
on the way to the store
so I didn't have money to pay for my cigar
so maybe I'll wait for that to charge for a minute
7% okay
Yeah it was kind of interesting day
yesterday. Hi Rudy, Rudy are you making noise?
You said I have a meow
You got a meow back
You got a meow back? Okay
Hi I'm over here
Hi baby
Hi, is that Lola?
Hi Lola. The cat RVs are stacked.
What's up?
Yeah, so I don't know.
Yesterday was kind of crazy because I think it was like we're gonna wake up sometimes it's like the day this takes off like yesterday
It's like, you know
Moke up. It's like, oh
Let's see what's other betas and you know, there's elbow back. They're all fighting
And then he drops the bomb. Yeah, there's Rudy. He drops the bomb. He said, well, Vita, you didn't
Give me Sykes, Sykes' information for me to go after him and start harassing him. And she denied it and stuff
I started a live. He came over here. He showed the proof
She shared some kind of like, I guess she must have, I don't remember her ever sending me something through Zella
It's usually through Cash App, okay? Like, okay, one second, but uh
But she sent my phone number, my legal name and stuff to him.
This is several months ago that this happened, but it's been a secret, you know?
Something that I could never have proved.
Hi, great bull.
Here's the link for the chat.
Aw, there's Rudy.
Here's an iPod tie.
But, you know, and then I turned into something like, you know, Sam Man started a show, then
Alex started a show.
I mean, I was like, it was going crazy, okay, so let's swap them.
Hi, and X. Hi, and X. Hey, that bitch is crazy. Let her come to Houston. She's about to lose her job at Amazon. They've called me and I've told them everything and I have a police report on her. Amber was telling the truth on your live. She does have warrants out for her rest.
There's a reason she left Houston and I have the address. We went over there, took pictures and I'll probably post it.
And she keeps going on about my age and I'm sickly and all this shit
I wouldn't have been discharged out of that facility if if I was still in bad shape because they planned on keeping there me there for a long
Time because actually I couldn't even sit up. I
Wasn't doing what I was supposed to do. I was out in the heat and you know and I got sick
And I wasn't drinking water and it started causing an issue with my right kidney with not enough water
And I got so sick. I was
practically crawling around my apartment for three days.
And somebody called the ambulance on me
when I went out to try to go to the doctors and I fell.
And so I'm fine because they told me
I probably wouldn't be out of there for a while
because they said, you know, you're in bad shape
because I was in ICU hooked up to machines
like her dad was.
Right, I know.
And you saw me walking around the pool.
I'm tan, I'm very healthy.
Right, and I got a mountain bike and I'm going to get on my bike again. So yeah
Yeah, I mean, it's like, you know, I'm sure they're going to come over here. So amazon is aware of her. I did contact her supervisor
and they told me to send all this evidence on her.
She's a nut.
She worked for remote and I showed them everything
she texted to me and the police are aware.
So let her come over here because she doesn't even know
where I moved to.
Nobody knows.
Yeah, my family have lost.
Yeah, because I had to go to my old place to get some mail.
Yeah.
Because I'm still changing the address
and I had to redo my ID and all.
I think that if I was to listen to you think that is about everything and then what would it be so it's my channel and so all the side who comes here and who needs to go okay so like for example beta needs to go because beta docs me the elder and that's been proven now here's what Karen does Karen okay I'm sorry if you let me go for a second I just want to say
You, you came in, you know, you're very, you have a good heart.
You're very generous and you had people start to betray you.
Just kind of like, I have, but I didn't have the proof at first.
You, you're smart enough to start logging some of some of these things of this abuse.
Yeah, I keep track of everything.
I already put a couple of people.
I was working with the FBI when we got rid of this guy, Tom.
You know, I'm not going to say his name and I wanted to record here in
California for years and.
And I got with the FBI and I'm still friends with the guy that helped me out. We were all over the news
So i'm even letting them know because she's full of shit. I'm gonna come over. She's a coward
Like tomi said she walks fast when she gets out of her car
Well, that was true like when we I did meet her and um
And when we just like, you know, we walked to you we'd gotten her car
I think we were smoking a joint or whatever, but it was kind of like i'm a fast walker. Yeah, she was right up with me
and she's like a fast walker too. I don't know. I'm not always looking over my shoulder.
She's very worried because she's wanted everywhere. She's got a lot of warrants and
it's true what Amber said, but I didn't know Amber. That's why they want to be on the panel
and she's going around showing that. So she's a strong person now and she's showing everything.
well you know somebody else is like now somebody else like I saw these pictures I just want you
to refute these because um you know the bq person has now shown pictures of huge rats and and
saying that it's your house I don't know if you've seen that no I don't live in a house I live in a
new town and I'm not gonna have rats there's no rats here I mean it's like I've never seen a rat
like the biggest it looks like you know like nature the main channel rat is great
Yeah, he's right now. You go to his community wall, there's a picture of the front of the house.
Yeah, he can't see this and I blocked him everywhere. That's what he's going off and
then he's lying about Ganville and making up shit. Ganville is not a peddle.
Ganville spoke about that kid and I remember seeing that, that they had a kid on panel about
stream yards or whatever and it was somebody else that had him up.
Yeah, and people were just criticizing him because he was he was becoming I think he was a juggalo then I think yeah
And it was an innocent but he's lying and saying all this shit about him and he's obsessed with them
Now he's obsessed. I guess when you cut him off for good. Yeah nuts, and that's what they said
He's saying that he's saying that he cut me off, you know, like in the you know, we did him
He was trying to get on your panel and all
And here I was defending him but don't know because he says Alex gave him, um, then he said $4,000
Yeah, and I shared a post of what he said about the other one shit to do with her because she keeps yeah
She's I mean she's just crazy, but I should have never supported him
But I never supported him with money or anything. I haven't given other people money only the people I mentioned
Now you have bad boy that was a rogue and I'm glad Brandon called him out
I didn't realize he was shady and he's lying and lying saying I gave somebody a computer. I've never given anybody a computer
Accusing you've been pretty bad stuff today too. No, it's he's a criminal and he was stalking and following a boy
And he went to jail for that and crystal even put it out there and it is true. That's what happened
He's a weirdo. He's a beast and he lays in bed. Gia used to show us his pictures
He doesn't get out of the bed. He just lays there and they made fun of him for that
Have you ever seen that picture? Have you ever seen that right there? Have you seen that before? Whatever that is?
No, what is that? It's it's it's Karen aka. This is brandon's wall. He says he says he lives in a dump not rich
Uh, you're kidding. He's crazy. He's my apartment. Those were nice. Look at where he lives. Look at that rat. Look at that mouse
Yeah, right. Where did that come from? There's I've never seen him as big of a rat in my life, right?
That looks like more like him than anything I've ever seen.
It looks like he's going to gamble line
and put in all these weird pictures
and everybody knows it.
Like that donation from Alex to him,
it's his writing because he can't spell.
Yeah, it's kind of obvious, you know?
It's like, you know, he can just.
Yeah, everybody knows that
because everybody's reaching out, they were mad at me.
And I knew I should have never given them a chance
because, you know, a lot of people were pissed off.
Kate, Barry.
yeah i mean even lately he's like fuck hers he's over there talking to the petal uh you know
they were pissed so i'm done with him but he's got mental issues i have his address i privy
did it he can't do anything about it but he lives in the dump did you see it
They don't even have a pool, nothing.
It's just an embarrassment.
And he went to my parents' home in Albuquerque
in zip code 87109, and he was impressed
because I'd lived there when I went finished high school.
But he's a loser, and his family didn't want him
because he went crazy on them.
And so he threw him away, I guess,
and an uncle or somebody tried to raise him.
Yeah, yeah, he's crazy with the pictures. You know what you can see the picture and see Google it
It'll show you where he's getting it and and he's getting it from Google or whatever. Yeah
Who's gonna take pictures of rats? No, there's no rats in a property. I've never been around rats
Yeah, I live in a nice place and look at him. He lives. That's probably the rats at his place. I
Never see
The dump and my brother goes to Albuquerque and he's gonna go there
In three weeks and I gave him the address and that's something you don't fuck with. Yeah, he'll get everything over there
But still he's sick. Okay. Well, hold on a second. I don't you're someone coming up
But I don't know how long this will last. I'm sick. Hello. Yo, I next you was sucking Brandon Q. Dick
now what happened you know what's at salmon i didn't realize he was crazy i tried we
had psyche psyche you know crazy you're crazy too man you don't know the truth you don't know the
truth you know what i'm saying man that we're working is apparently you and i and elder are
all working together conspiring i don't give a fuck about you i don't give a fuck about i
Okay, well, I don't know about you get talking about what happened with elder. He's working with one. Yeah. Yeah
I'll show you this post I got yesterday. I was posted and it will show
I'll just read it actually, I'll just read it.
So it's my discourse, someone sent it to me.
And then read and lied because that was her
in that group chat, you know, those are true.
This is what is being said about you publicly.
So you can just like, you know,
I was trying to give you a chance
to don't give a fuck about us.
Okay, well, I'll give a fuck about you.
What did they say about him?
Yeah. Okay, so it says, let me grab this.
It says right here, it says,
as of today, the son of,
and then of course my parents' names, okay?
is aligned with a known criminal harasser
who targets people on others' behalf for money.
He's known as Eldo.
Eldo in the past has stated on multiple occasions,
he would physically assault me, hold on.
And then it has some, it says Eldo is directly affiliated
with Samman NYC.
Samman NYC is orchestrating the situation
between Bita's kiddies, Eldo and Psyche behind the scenes,
specifically to control Bita,
force her to continue her relationship with him.
Although psyche and salmon will likely attempt to extort beta as long as salmon NYC is in her life
She will likely face trouble. Hopefully God steps in so I'll give him a chance to respond to that
But if he's rude, I'm just gonna kick his ass off again because I'm not
Alexander mayors said that
Yeah, she's talking about him and me. You know, she said it was me working with Sam and Elza.
Yeah, I don't know what the issue is with her. She's mad because I reported a lot of her videos
and they took it down.
Yeah, well, I mean, she's still on and she's, you know, and she thinks I'm not going to do anything about it. Yes, I can come over here, man. I'll protect myself, you know, just like somebody who did when, you know, and they told me I can and she's a coward.
She's not going to show up here. Meet me at your apartment B, B seven Alex or in Florida.
And I can tell you her address because she fucked up by putting her address on her trying to fight a report. I did on her. She put her full address on there and it's been confirmed to have her address.
Yeah, I don't know. I think I'm not saying Alice is correct in her assumption. I'm not gay after all
Okay, you guys can come to your own conclusion about that
I guess you know and I just feel bad for her. She just flips on everybody and she's insane and you know
I would never give her another chance. She does this with everybody even chicken cakes
I mean everybody Carissa and Trisha
I mean, like every, she doesn't even have any friends.
I mean, she's always all alone all the time.
A lot of times you hear me with friends in the background,
you know, they're my best friends.
And like that video below, my best friend's mom, you know,
is taking care of those other cats and trying to find homes.
Like I said, I get everybody involved and we work together.
And she didn't think care about that all she cares about drama and these lies and shit
You know and they see everything because we her information is out and I gave it to our attorney
Yeah, but first I had to talk to Amazon
Yeah, so now they're aware and she's probably gonna lose her job because I'm showing them everything
They asked that any time she posts or anything shows do you have anything?
Yes, and I have their email so she needs a shut up
She's not gonna make it to my age. She's already having issues right now
You know, but I'm a hundred percent healthy and she probably won't recognize me when she sees me and
Like I said, I'm gonna protect myself
Well, yeah, I mean it's like that's the thing
It's like I think of like a lot of the smearing where she's kind of an expert expert at spearing people, you know
She's laughing at her all these streamers tell me oh, she's a nut and I said well
Why do you some of you go along with her?
And they don't and she had made a fool of herself joining Zayas and peps live
I have that video and they humiliated her they were laughing at her and he was shaking his head like get the fuck off
And as soon as she dropped off he was shaking his head and he said that cock-eyed bitch and peps was laughing at her
Yeah, talk about how she flip-flops so much like why the hell does she join?
their panel, you know, she's just
and saying, so she's me smearing salmon too.
I mean, what is her, she's fucked up.
Well, yeah, she was on yesterday with Crystal Ann
and she was like, she's actually said,
I heard on fan man, she was saying,
well, he was playing her clip, but she said,
she said, well, she's like, I think all the men
in this community want to assault the women.
And then she said that the men,
she called us all rapists.
She said we're all rapists or rapists.
You know what she said?
She said all the men are rapists.
That's so bad.
Because she just seems so intelligent and sometimes she could be cool. Yeah. It's get so her sister. I have talked to her and she said she has a personality disorder.
And I said, well, how do you mean? And she described exactly how she acts. And I said, well, I got some videos to show you and I did play that recording of her talking about her sister that I haven't posted. I have a lot to post going crazy and how she wanted.
Like she wants Zaya, like I'm just more interested in your conversation with a certain person about Zaya.
You know, like, damn, because she was trying, you know, like, like she said, she's coming
over here and she showed up across the street from him.
And I have that recorded because she asked me to record it.
Yeah, that's when she said, get a gun or something like that.
Yeah.
And I got it back because I just didn't post it again because I showed them her communication
asking me to share it because she wanted me to, you know, record it.
And she was getting drunk and then she's calling him out to come to the restaurant.
He waited a while and he finally showed up and he had a backpack. He didn't pull up a gun or anything
She wasn't expecting him to show up and then she turned around like she's scared and ran like a like a dumbass
And pretended to call the police and she disappeared when she was desperate for him and come over there
Right, I mean it's a little bit odd. Yeah, I mean but I think that she knows people know the truth about her
Especially that she's that she's in relationships with and then so when she turns on them
She has to smear them in order that they're not believed and she's really good at playing like the racial
Angle and the woman angle with it, right? She'll start to collect together all all these women that were formerly enemies and then
I mean, she's basically, Christine and Bita are her number ones now, and if you remember...
Not for long, yeah, not for long, because she does this to everybody. Everybody be careful, man.
I mean, I remember that time she sent that Melissa to me, because she wanted to take me to Olive Garden
or Red Lobster and that Melissa messaged me on Discord.
So I went to her chat the next day and she was like, Oh, yeah, I'm gonna invite you.
And it's like, bitch, after what you've done before, but I should have never given her another chance.
I really thought she she was a good person or yeah, I mean, the thing is, like, you know,
like the first go around, yeah, I saw like, you know, there's signs of something weird,
but it's like, it seemed like the first time that it seemed like it was all everything was my fault.
And so I was actually trying to apologize to her.
And then she made this big thing, except it's my apology.
Then all of a sudden, I'm getting flowers at the door.
I got this big bouquet of yellow roses.
And then I'm getting, and then, you know,
and we were just, we were back friends again.
And it's like, and then for those few months,
it was, I guess it was April, May, June.
It was pretty, I never had one problem with her.
Like she never, she never, not one negative interaction.
And then it's like, but she turns,
now it's not one positive interaction.
It's so extreme that
You know, it's like now I can and it will ramp up every time every time that you will accept your back
It will get worse and worse every time and it's like, you know, it'll be good again. I mean, that's like the honeymoon period
That's the uh, the the Hoover period when they when the when a narcissist hooverers you back up
It starts with love bombing again, and these are people that are like kind of been yeah, right?
Go ahead and go ahead finish we've just been stepped on and we're we're at this point where nobody nobody and somebody comes
Oh here there's there's a friendly person again, and we're like I got suckered into it
You know I have to say you know like like at that time you should have just left it alone
That's right. Right here parents and I guess me. Oh, yeah
Sensitive and you know like I think we are and it's hurtful because she goes hard like I did like I used to I used to go hard on
these people psyche
I did some real life shit and no, I'm not going to do that again though, you know, and I feel great
I'm happy. I don't do drugs like I used to I didn't give a shit then well
That's one thing it's like it's like you take responsibility for maybe some negative things you've done as as do I
Yeah, I did she's done nothing wrong according to her you know ever basically she's like a saint. She's like a
She's like a military strategist where she's giving Brandon Q these cheat codes on how to beat us.
He's apparently the smartest out of us.
All of a sudden, I'm Canadian. I've never been to Canada. I was born in Richmond Hospital in New York.
Right.
Me and my brother, that's a year younger than me, were born in the States.
Our younger siblings were born in other countries.
It's so sick now. I mean, it's sick. And I gave that horrible Brandon Q a chance.
Calling me a you know a pedia. I mean, it's like him calling. I mean it's like all of a sudden
It's like upside-down clown world
It's a it's a what what's that about that because he is a smart guy and we got into it and I found that he's sensitive too
You know, so I didn't mean to hurt him back or what I did because I try to remember the
You know the good conversations we've had and I think he was hurt that you kicked him off and because I was gonna tell you
earlier hey
Let him up on there, but you know just no yelling, but he was right about bad boy when he went off on him
Okay, right, and then look at how you found that bad boy what he did to gia
He was blocking everybody that he's shady. He has
Crazy rants that he does on his lives about my neighbors that has guns this person this is
Everybody talked about him doing that
But yeah, he got a Nancy called the police on him because he was showing his dad's police badge and he almost was taken to jail.
But yeah, he has a record of him following and stalking a young boy. So that is true. And I defended him on that because Crystal posted it and it's true.
Yeah, that crystalline is now she's now she's she kind of gets blown around by the wind to this crystal and like you know
She was on Alex's ignore her. I'm not contacting her family or anything or sending anything. I left that
I don't think any of us. I think that it's like, you know, family should be looked out of it really
It's like, you know, she knows about
Brandon and everything I was defending him to her. But yeah, I don't know why he keeps on
I guess he can't stand it when when you're done with them. But what he did was wrong, you know
I mean, and probably like he has he's sensitive. I don't know, but
Gave him a chance. It's like, you know what he was right about bad boy because I think that's what got you mad though
Too that he seemed to be attacking him, but it's like he knew
Yeah, well, I don't know about bad boy, like bad boy, like his messages seem like a little bit schizophrenic that I've seen.
Yeah, he is schizophrenic, yes.
He's accusing you of things now and his book.
I don't talk to him. He's the one that started following me and sharing my stuff, and then somebody showed me how tooth-faced he was yesterday, and that's what I saw.
And that's what it's like. So I said something about it, but I'm not talking about his past, because I was the one that showed it in the first place.
Right.
And that lady right Renee on top who did investigations and stuff, she called him out.
Yeah, but who knows he's probably lying about crystal saying he was on the phone with her the night that she said somebody drove over her toe, but that guy is back at Vienna he said his name is Vienna Milano.
He's back on YouTube.
Okay.
I mean, I drove over her toe.
I mean, imagine how difficult it would be for a car
to drive over somebody's toe.
That sounds like the Nicki Minaj story
where she got shot in the foot by some guy.
Right, and she said the girlfriend did it.
And that's why I have the clip of Chelsea, his girlfriend,
saying that she didn't even know Crystal,
and she was accused of that.
And so she reached out to her on IG to ask her,
what's going on?
You know, who are you?
Who are you?
And I have that.
I still have that.
There we go. Yeah, I'm not gonna walk. Who knows what happened then, but bad boy said he was on the phone with her till 3.30 till she fell asleep.
Why didn't he say that before?
Right. All this information is coming out. Interesting times. Okay, hold on.
So maybe it happened. We don't know what happened that night. All I know is that she did freak out.
and he was the one on the phone with her.
Yeah, I was familiar with a lot of these people.
Yeah, he's just weird and you saw his,
everybody sees his YouTube and they said,
man, he sounds like a schizo and it's like he is.
About his neighbors and shots outside, he's paranoid.
So yeah, and I couldn't believe that you said that he was blocking people.
Now, remember he did that to Gia and
others because he's whacked and he's paranoid.
So everything he's saying about yeah
Well, yeah, I think Brandon and both both
Yeah, here you would oh, I think Brandon is now saying he'd like he's like w crystal
He's like he's so Brandon is it like it's bad and he says he's he's a pedo and she's sticking with that
Yeah, that's what she got mad at me because I talked to him and she can't stand them and she says he's a pedo and
All of that and she was even saying that last night someplace and yeah
But I don't know but he called bad boy out and so I don't know what his issue is because that was gonna leave it alone
I didn't know he was still going on about it. He just can't stand rejection
I guess but I knew I should have never gotten involved with him though. Everybody warned me
Um, Barry, Kate, I mean, she wouldn't even let me on panel because you're supporting a pedo.
A lot of them been saying that, you know, and here I was gonna, it was like, you know, he is
intelligent. He just has angry, angry issues. And I don't like that the way he blew up on you,
on, on your panel for no reason. Yeah. You know, and the thing is with like psychopaths or a lot
of them have a high intelligence and it's like they're using it in such a negative way.
or they're twisting it, or just playing online.
Or they think, you know, way with like flat out lies
because they smear the person so much.
Like, I've been so smeared.
You've been smeared.
I know and I've had a lot of people that don't even know us.
Well, maybe it's me too and everybody sees the truth. Yeah, but that lady called my youngest brother
a year ago and I didn't know it until recently, you know, and she was acting cool with me. It's
like, are you sure? But he did say, but the voice didn't match. So it's like, who else would it been?
You just told me
who she was and you saw the channel and he said I just know it was a wiki info site and the woman
said it was hers and you're doing meth and that's how you lost way more weight than you did before.
Yeah, I mean, it's like she does have like a presentation that that kind of is like people will think it's credible because she speaks very well and
intelligently
Yeah, she graduated high school. I did I graduated from colleges with the finance degree and she's working at a call center
That's for Amazon
Yeah, I mean and it's like I don't even know I mean it's like I
I mean, I don't want to almost get as low as they're getting because they're, I mean, they're taking it so low and I would never go as low as they're getting.
Some people do because two people found my, got my college information.
Oh, yes, she did graduate with a bachelor's and it's like, Dean, that's fucked up that you're going to go that far.
That's why nobody said anything because I graduated with a finance degree and a minor in Spanish.
Okay, we have...
It looks like somebody's backstage, but I think it's just Brandon. So I'm just
Yeah, until he chills because you know what he is a smart guy
I like talking to him and this thing just went nuts
And then we fought and started talking, you know saying shit at each other
But I kind of missed the combos I had with him because he's smart
And he's not too faced. I thought he was too faced for a while and it's I see that he's not
Well, he came on yesterday and sort of torn bombing me and started using the N word, so I just have to be really careful right now.
So what are you saying? You know, he's sensitive like we are, maybe give him a chance and it's like, it's just so much has been going on with real shitty people though.
And he wasn't shitting, you know, and I see I respect him for not being so to face and doing what everybody does is hate bonding all of that and and he's right about gamble.
And I was telling the truth because that came out yesterday on the panel about the Daniel. He was 12 years old.
Right, well, I mean that that's you like, you know, even like, you know, people have people can have different
I don't know if that kid had the parents permission to be on the show
I don't know if they can think of the pair
I don't know that really the details to like and so even having somebody on your show that does not make somebody
I would say a pdf, but there are other
Yeah, he was on the show. He was on the show. So I don't think that's pdf
But the the picture of him with that little kid out in the water. That's just that's kind of suspect
Right, okay. Oh, there's bad boy breeze in the chat. He goes she is. Oh my god. You need to ban him
He's just a piece of shit bad boy
I'm gonna put everything out there with your case and crystal wasn't lying about you you screwed her over
You were not on the phone with her till three o'clock in morning because you never mentioned that
So who knows but Vienna is back and he was all over in that chat yesterday
He's he's in the chat and I tagged him to video. I don't even know why you have him on there because all he does is fuck with people
Lies and he's paranoid as fuck
And he's on a mod and Nancy and Jamie. I've never given them anything. They sent me gifts
I've never sent out. No Nancy. I sent her
a dinner for Olive Garden for her birthday,
but she always sent me more.
She sent me a lot of stuff from Lush, flowers,
and so did Jamie.
I've never sent Jamie anything.
And no, I never sent anybody a computer.
It was somebody else that had a computer to give away,
and she was gonna give it to Crystal,
who got paranoid and thought maybe it was bugged
or something.
Right, well, I mean, that's what they,
I mean, there's a group of people that they do send gifts
that are like, you know, I guess they sent this guy a microwave.
The first one was like, um, like, um, invaded by like crickets or something.
And he got this guy got these bugging bugs throughout his house
because they sent him microwaves and stuff like that.
And they did it twice on a road to him.
And just like, just like, kind of like Cyrax, they would send Cyrax
up like a little USB thing for his Xbox and then it would kill the Xbox.
And he put it in three times, killed three Xboxes like that.
You know, so there are people that will send these like, I guess,
Trojan horse kind of gifts.
That's where it gets so crazy with some of the stuff, but it's like, I mean, it's very
devious and sick.
I mean, I'm going to buy a cigar real quick.
I'll just address the chat real quick.
I just have to put some money in my up.
I'll be right back.
Yeah, somebody, Jared is in there, asking, saying he's not Brandon, so I don't know.
I don't know that person.
Give me a few minutes, Jared, because I'm just going to go, I'll be right back.
Sure.
Okay, okay, I got my baby here. Thank you. Let's check out the chat
Hey
Well, you got to let them see who it is, you know, like to open their camera or whatever for you
So they don't porn volume porn volume. Maybe you're so quiet
You need a meow, baby
Okay
Is that a person or not somebody trying to porn bone view? I know off the way off the way to like
Thank you so much
Because I need to be at my computer, basically.
But, yeah, well, let's see, why ban everyone scumming Audi?
I didn't ban one person, actually.
Thing that is so, like, you're wrong about that.
I didn't ban anybody.
I'm on my phone right now.
I actually can't even ban if I wanted to.
That's why I'm not bringing the person up.
But, you know what?
What I noticed about Karen is that she's a very honest person,
and she always has the receipts to back it up.
Like, she doesn't make up anything.
Yeah, she said it. Yeah, everybody sees that.
Yeah.
And so I just got a stick of a cigar,
I'm on my way back home.
Okay, and then I'll check out, I'll check on the chair,
but it's like the person's not on,
I don't know that person and they're not up on the,
it sounds like a name that he would use before,
so I'm not sure who it is,
for why they're here, but it's not like that.
I just told him I'm a guest here, I can't, you know,
it's not, this isn't my panel.
What happened to bad boy?
I didn't hide bad boy, I don't know if anybody did,
but bad boy is like, you know,
Posting stuff about you know accusing people of murder and stuff like that and yeah, he's crazy
He almost was put in jail for flashing pretty crazy, right badge and he got scared. That's why he doesn't fuck with Nancy
Okay
Yeah, so he's always threatened to pull up to her house. So he was threatening to pull up to somebody's house
So that's why charisma charisma I trust my mods and I think that is I've offered you mod
You know you but you didn't want it. So right
Trying to pull up on you bad boy. He's a coward. No bad boys. Bad boys threatened to pull up at your house. Yeah
Oh, really? Bad boy, you were scared when somebody was going to pull up at your place.
Remember, we have your information and you're the one that's the pedo.
You were following a 14-year-old boy and it's in your background.
So come on, you coward.
You're not going to pull up because you've been scared of me.
He's so scared of everybody.
I'll put his information out there because Nancy almost went over there and he got scared
and hid and lied about her.
Right.
Yeah, I mean it's like
Some of these people I think it's just better to totally detach from and not interact with them because it's like that just gets them
It's some ammunition and I mean sometimes when you respond to somebody that that's exactly what they want because that gives them more material
To to expand upon for their for their stuff and it's like that's all they're trying to do
They're trying to become credible
they're trying to become relevant and some of these people should just remain irrelevant and not credible because
You know, no matter what and see him in a chat, I was gonna say something to him because now he's gonna block that
logic about
His dad is his caretaker. No, no, no real life threats
Yeah, he's got a bunch of chickens that he killed is what they said
I thought yeah, I said that he's rescuing them and somebody who knows them said no he kills them or
You know and then the dog that he threw out. I don't know what that was a farmer
Is he living on chicken farm or like what like I don't know
He's out there in the country and then people go out there and shoot because there's a lot of like country
And then he said they were coming to shoot him. No, they have like a little shooting range out there
and he's just paranoid and he's scared of people,
so he ain't gonna pull up anywhere
because I would be glad to meet him.
He's a punk and he's real huge from what they said.
Gio said that he always laid on the couch
when they FaceTimed.
He was never off that couch and he's huge.
And the other people that saw him said the same thing
and Victoria Honeykid really called him out
and he's just scared of people.
But he's just so shady
because he's paranoid and crazy, you know?
I mean, yeah, I just didn't like him.
And then there he was following me and then going at Crystal.
And Crystal was not on the phone with him till 3.30 that night.
He lied because that came out years later.
Well, I know I did hear that Crystal likes to like, you know,
you have to talk to her until she falls asleep when she talks to you.
Yeah.
And then there's a big.
There's a big like, there's a noise when she's on like the shows, you hear like this kind of rustling that's rubbing sound. Yeah. Yeah. She was rubbing around in her bed, you know, and she ignores that everyone else is like, what is that? Everyone kind of ignores it's kind of funny.
Even cute.
You said that's you because she tried to lie, but there's videos on her about them filming her while she, you know, with her phone on discord. It's like, it's sad. She's worse than she was before because when I talked to her through the months before she actually started being active.
She sounded normal, and I remember one time I was going to go and react to something and
she was trying to talk me out of it and then there she shows up and she's back into all the BS.
And all, you know, and me too though, you know, it's not just her and we got to fight and it's like, you know, we're better, you know, outside of this position that we're, we have to lower ourselves to go by it's like fighting in the mud with pigs and the pig likes it and then we get dirty kind of thing and sometimes better just to like, let them come up to us rather than going down to their level.
because they're
People know my background. My mom's father was a politician. So I mean she has a lot of money
You know her family my dad made a lot of money too, but not like her
You know, he's an oil man and she's working her life or anything
She traveled all over the world sometimes with her sisters and her mom was German
Jewish because they left the Holocaust when before she was born
and then they went to South America,
Chile and her mom passed away giving birth to her.
Her dad, I guess he was broken up over it.
He took his life and she was adopted by a Chilean family.
Then she married my grandfather.
I showed Alex the guide that my mom was engaged to
before she took off and married my dad.
You know yeah, okay. Yeah, so I'm just gonna go back in my house. I'll be right back good back, okay?
You're doing a lot of sleep in little baby
You sleepy
Little's where are you? I go find her. Why are you? Oh, oh boy cat?
Yeah, hi guys
Well anybody else want to come up? They're welcome up right now. I mean because now I can check check and verify
Who everyone is and so I'm back in my house
I mean having crazy dreams all morning. I dreamed I kind of like was with the Samoan family
I don't there is some Samoan in a pats life, but
Everything there is everything their house is big because they're all big people. It's everything that's bigger
It's not a kind of interesting. I don't know I just woke up today like
kind of like wow a lot of stuff has happened a lot of stuff is happening and it's like just to keep up with it, but it's like
At the end of the day
I have made some friends back, you know that that's good and people that have left me to the people that said
Oh, you're I'm glad you're away from that Brandon guys. I did but you know if they had such an issue
I'm not even trusting them anymore
Right
Motives for things and there's other personal things going on
I had I mean it's like it's in order to keep up with it. I mean I would need basically, you know a full-time, you know
High-powered AI like you know mapping out every single relationship and and figuring out the stuff
So I can't quite you know get in the middle and judge other people's relationships
I can only judge but judge by own in my own personal experience, right?
And so yeah, and so focus on our real-life relationships, and I'm happy with that and especially my family, you know, we're close
Yeah, but it's unfortunate, like, I know, like, you know, just the amount of screaming
and slandering and hate I got because of, like, you know, one time putting in a thumbnail
someone that beauty used to know or something like that, and then when she asked, I took
it down, but, and she just acted like, you know, such a violation, but then here she
is sharing my information with people who knows will heard.
Yeah, because like every time I get text messages often saying leave beat it alone leave beat alone you and it's like
I'm like, who is this? I mean, it's like I didn't think that I mean, yeah
It's like I think it's that Britney Spears guy that was like bleep pretty alone
It's like that it's just like it doesn't make any sense some of these messages
I can I can't really show them because they always put pictures of mini Manson in there with like a razor blade to his vagina
Oh my god, what are they messaging you at on IG cuz I don't
No, my personal number my my real phone number. Oh, wow. Yeah, I never give out my real number
He just but that's I mean it was it was they got it through Zell
I mean it was given it was through I should be to had my number
But she's but instead of like, you know, just giving him the number she sent him something was up
So here's this Jared Juggernaut's backstage and so I'm gonna put up my thing real quick
We'll find out who it is one second. Yeah, you're gonna check it out because you said that Brandon try to form bomb you
Yeah, we'll get ready for maybe a possible form bomb. But here
Hello. Hello. Who's this? This is Jared. Okay. Hi, Jared. What's up? How's it going? Hi? You sound normal. Okay. Oh
You're looking guy. Oh fitness. I need a personal trainer. You look like Wolverine a little bit
Jared. Hey, Jared. You did a lot. Yeah, okay. Well, I'll talk to you after the show. So what's up? How are you?
I'm good. How are you? I'm excellent. Wow
Very good looking guy. So how are you part of this community or how'd you find my show?
I'm an n-word bomber. I came to say nigger. Oh, you did. Oh, you did. Oh my gosh. Why would you do that? Oh, he said so though
He said what do you say? I think he said vinegar. He's giving us a recipe. I
Yeah, that's weird so that's a picture. Oh, there's beta. Oh, please see my community posts
I'll be making shorts of all the times that's like he dogs. Okay. I want to see all the time
I dox you show me one time where I shared your phone number beta, okay, and show me one time. Okay said your last name
I've never known her to be a doctor because we'd get into it or anything, and I don't think she ever doxxed or anything
Other you know
Okay, so be it. Yeah, that was when I first started my show. I did have a PayPal that was my name, right?
But it still didn't have my phone number on it, right? I mean I shared my last name
That's not a big deal saying my name is not a big deal
I shared that but actually sharing my phone number with somebody
Giving it to them and saying go after this person and even prove and be that be that I know I know it's I know you're
Squeaky clean image is gone. You know you were so innocent
You seem like such an innocent person that never did anything to anybody have a beautiful beautiful day. Well you too, be the your doxer, okay?
I want to say something to clear this up. Her two other ex-friends said that Barb was
lying about her ever being 5150 and they were pissed off that I did that interview with her.
Crystal was on a panel saying that it was Nancy and Jamie were the ones that did it. No, they
were mad because they said she didn't have no 5150 done when we talked to her more than Barb.
Um, yeah, but I didn't say that it was uh, Jamie and you know, that's bullshit crystal
You lied because it was barb and she admitted it on the panel that it was her that said it
Yeah, and I remember my phone number on the air, but you know, it's like it's kind of kind of ridiculous
So there's the adobe. Oh, yeah, so whatever the jeer was. I was probably just branding with the good boy. I don't know
I'm an n word bomber
I mean it was like it didn't sound like him. I don't think it sounded like it would have sounded like like a Peewee Herman
Keep my name out of your mouth. Hey, keep keep keep my name and my phone number out of your text messages to people be to how about that bitch
You guys were friends though psyche, you know, don't I know but you know what she turned against me
You know why because of because of Arthur saying something ever since then she would not let me apologize because she thought she had something over and
Begging I mean a hundred times. I'm apologize. You know, I've been so nice
So many times and it's like and she will not stop with me and every time I flip on her show
There's my name. Oh, did my name my name my name and she said I talked about her all the time
Keep your name out of my mouth. How about that bitch? Okay. I mean geez you got more money than you do you promise me?
Wow, it's a money contest what
What are you going to do?
You're going to hire a hit man, Bita?
Like, what are you doing?
Like, what, who cares about how much money you have?
OK, it's not the heart, not about the money.
You're so superficial.
Well, some people do have a lot of money.
I know my family does, so I don't need to work or anything.
But I made a lot of money on my own, though, too.
But I'm retiring early, or I might go back to work.
I'm bored, so I might do that.
Like I said, I'm a lot more with the rescue.
Yeah, I'm not moving anything.
I'm not moving anything, because whatever I shared has no,
full name on it. It has her like, you know, a screen name of hers. It has my full name
on it and my phone number and it's sending it to people, right? That are known that are
known doctors and so right. So
And Carl she made a pact with Carl, but you know what Carl was just working for beta
Actually, we figured out like trying to get her out of the way
I mean, that's why he said that because he was on the next day, too. I thought I'd been Carl
We're going next day. Yeah, and he's had a lot to say about her. So yeah, I don't know him
I don't know why he keeps jumping on and keeps trying to talk to me. I don't know the guy
I don't like what he did to beta
And to that other lady because I don't know it just doesn't make sense because that lady said he did a lot to her and now she's hiding or something.
Yeah, so I don't want to get into that. I don't know him. But yeah, that was weird and then all of a sudden he's
The next day he shows up commenting. So no, that's why I said, I don't want him on panel with me
He was wanting to do a live on beta and was asking me to join a month ago. Remember
Right. And you know what?
She had her fingers crossed and I think he did too because he was right on the on a different alt on YouTube the next day
Right. He was yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So he's had that account for a while. So he's got a bunch of alts. Yeah
you know that, yeah. And so, yeah, it's just kind of like ridiculous, you know.
And I'm the one that recorded the live when he jumped on crystals. I'm the one that put it out
there because he said he wasn't on other panels and she mentioned that he was already on,
on, what was his name? Clumsies, Clumsies.
I was the one that recorded him and that's when people saw that he lied because he was on clumsy's panel before that
Oh, he is on our way to the police department. By the way, isn't that funny? She's on our way to the police department
So what are you gonna show you to show you doxy me? I hope that they arrest her
I hope that they arrest her, you know when she goes to the police department because I didn't dox
I mean what what what is my arrestable offense? I want I would love to be I would love to go to court for this
I would love it because you know what I would win. It's not about how much money you have how good your lawyers are
Because I can't represent myself, you know, I can I need to
Sorry
The people here today doing that. Yeah the way she loves her capsule to and people said she pulled whiskers
No, but she used to give some good advice on cats and she I like the video
She said and she'd send and sometimes I shared
Mine too with her and she's the one that did voiceover on my sister's peeking ease in 2022
When she was happy, I still have that now she's big and they found out that she's small because she's a toy a toy
Piketty's she's so cute and she's real bitchy still
Yeah, you're and I still caught I still copy and I'm a Steve. I'm a Steve
Okay, I'm a Steve. Tell me a Steve if you want, but you know what I still copy
Steel copy so we have Terry Davis backstage. I noticed I know it's you Terry Davis. That's also George. I don't want to talk to him
He's a weird guy. No. Yeah, just a weird guy. Yeah
Yeah, see my commitment for my begging with yeah, be it a okay
Yeah, and make sure you go look at her her cash up that she puts on her on her screen
You know, it's okay for her to put her cash up up. It's not okay for me to promote my cash up, I guess and
But is that that stealing ask, you know asking for a donation. I mean, it's like that's how we kind of like, you know
Like it's how kind of YouTube works. I don't know it just turns into like is that illegal did I do anything illegal?
No, no, no, she's not going to the police department. She's in the fucking go probably probably and I
I liked her too. She likes her cats, you know, but whatever
She's
Definitely now proven a doctor and so now she's now she's embarrassed that she's trying to instead of just apologizing
You know instead of apologizing. Okay, she's gonna say that my chat. Well, you're banned
Okay, instead of apologizing and saying, hey, I did something wrong, like I would do like I apologize to her, right?
So you're banned, bitch. Okay, but I have all the talking private though. Don't get mad at her though.
You know, she's very well, I know
Yeah, she she had the innocent kind of thing
But it's like she the things that she said is like pretty much unforgivable
No, she's these hurt. She's angry and so are you so you guys were friends at one time. So just
Take some time out and talk when you can, but don't
I've tried I've tried I've tried but you know, it's like if she would if she was just to say I'm sorry
I did some that was a mistake. I would just forgive her and I'm not like going to the police about it or anything like that
I'm just
But but she's but she's instead of that she's deciding to go back and slander me instead
So go ahead and slander me go slander me on your own show. Okay. You're not gonna slander me in my own chat, bitch
I mean, are you crazy?
Don't call her a bitch, so you know what she is actually it means you I mean for that word if it's anybody it's definitely her because
Um, you know, who else is going to give my information to a doctor for no reason?
I mean, this was months ago and then lying.
Is this a hug box?
Get over here.
Okay.
I want to give Kate a hug.
Kate, Kate's in the chat.
So, you know, I know Kate hates me, but it's like, you know,
Kate is in the chat.
Yeah.
She was angry at me for talking about Brandon.
A lot of people were though.
And I'll, I'll be the bigger, I'll be a big person.
I'll, and I'll, she said, she's going to accept my apology, but I
apologize again.
And didn't she say you were, you apologized and she was right.
Okay.
So.
Yeah, yeah, you know and it shouldn't have been on live
Hey, I'm not Kate whoever if she's hidden. I didn't I didn't ask her to be hidden and she's fine to be in the chat. Oh
I mean that was wrong of Eldo because if he had that information before why didn't he say something before why now you know
Well, you know sometimes it's because he was you know because he he was you know
I'm managing mod in her chat and that was before she actually started put letting people put his his docks up his picture up and stuff like
That but then she would like kick off other people like that. Um, we're doing that same thing psyche. Let me
Brian, I know it's just you, Jared. We see the name. I mean, it's like, come on. It's like,
you're not my boo. You're going to say the N word to get a porn bomb. So why would I do that?
You don't see her? Maybe you're maybe. And then asking me like, like I'm running the panel. I
don't know him. I don't. But yeah, I mean, people say things out of anger. You guys were friends.
So I hope you guys talk outside of it. But although he looked bad because even Zaya and Pebs were
How shady he is and and they were doxing a peps was doxing his full name joe joe cruise or something
Doc them and they said that he can't do anything because they have his information still so i mean he
Yeah, it didn't make sense and how
He does this and they were laughing this said there's not going to be a part five part five where's a part five or five parts or
Whatever so i i don't know
yeah, but um
Yeah, I mean some of these people in behavior, but mine was pretty bad too a few years ago
Yeah, we've been through some stuff and it's like, you know, and that's why maybe you know
A lot of people have been have been traumatized and have and sometimes will react in weird ways and stuff like that
I think that is it might be it might be like you're looking at the like the top chat and not all chat turn it to all chat
She might show up start showing up in your comments if you do that
But you can look at the screen you can see the comments on the screen if I just turn it on so anyway
But I've but it's just a boy that she accepts the apology or not
I mean I was wrong and I do apologize to her and it's like and whatever was said or anything
I'm sorry for the things I said and it's like, you know
You know, there's things that are about me too, but you know, whatever it was, it's a, you know, it's forgiven on my side, but you're on live chat. Okay. Well, I don't know the thing that is you have to maybe I don't know why I don't know why. And so
Yeah, you can make an n-word tower and tell like a normal person, you know, you know, whoever's
Just do it. I got normal person
Okay, yeah
It's it's insane. You shouldn't have had uh him elbow up there. That's the only reason he came on there
He was doing a tour about beta and well, yeah
He looks bad himself
By waiting for so long and then all of a sudden he's
Talking about all that then and they have this information. Yeah, well, he was you know
He was good friends with her up to that up to that point
I guess and so but then you know when people turn on people like that and it's like and then they actually
they have like the truth about things. Sometimes the truth eventually comes out and so I am for
the truth coming out no matter what no matter what it is or why so I'm I am for the truth ultimately
right sometimes it takes longer to get to it because there's a lot of uh the gray area sometimes but
you know it's pretty hot today wow oh man here it's been raining a lot it's humid it's like every
day it stopped now but the last few days it kept raining all day long it's a hard rain
And yeah, yeah, that means we're probably gonna get a tropical storm because it's a it's a lot of rain
We've been getting yeah, hopefully not
Oh, and I saw the baby the baby cats mom outside, you know, so she's I don't see you're pregnant yet
But she was outside. I don't know where she's been. Yeah the baby and she's been missing
Yeah, well, maybe I can get her fixed or something but people were saying. Oh, no, she's pregnant
So yeah, I don't and if not then get fixed you might want to um
There are there are like some sometimes local organizations that look for those those cats that are not fixed and they go they don't fix them
They'll trim the little piece of their ear off. Yeah, they do. Yes. Yes. That's what I'm gonna
But I don't like them cut their ears. So I
I don't like it either and they didn't actually they the lady they actually took a couple of my cats to go fix and they
kept part of their ear off and it's like oh my god
It's like the reservoir dogs movie, you know, but uh, yeah, I mean I don't like that, but it apparently doesn't
her cat. I like what Bita had to say about the decline because when I was talking to Crystal,
she was talking about that, which she did that to her cat. And I think that it's safe now because
they do it by laser. So because of what Bita said, I looked into it and it's still just as bad.
They're pretty much cutting their bone and their toes off. Yeah, I mean, it's fine or anything.
They struggle later. It's like, you know, it's like, wow, it's that bad.
Yeah, I mean, I personally think that like the cats claws are they're kind of like that's they're kind of like defense like that
That's their there and it's like that's kind of taking away their defense. Plus it makes it harder to
Harder to
Yeah, they're like even the in the inside trees that you have for them. They struggle with that. Yeah crystal line
She was accused of killing
um Milo because she was ignoring Milo and Milo would hug her when she'd start freaking out online
a beautiful cat and then he started getting sick and and hiding in her closet and people were
her would tell her crystal take care of Milo you know and then her litter box was full of crap in
there and she didn't clean it so she was criticized i have the pictures but she didn't care and all of
He died and they found out that she had her dad take him to go get put down like she didn't want to mess with the cat
Cuz and she told me oh, he's old
No, you do the best you can like me. I always have I'm a I'm a
Advocate for the two of the biggest shelters here in the city
Yeah
This guy has been pain and suffering and it's like that thing that cannot be fixed. There's really no reason
to uh to to put the cat to sleep for old age i mean that's just uh well sometimes like like kitty was
really sick and she wasn't gonna make it so we've tried other options and you know so she got sick
and she passed away she was 20 almost 21 yeah you know but i know it hurts how people say you
know people will kill their cats because you know people say i did it because you know they're
that got by 50 and stuff like that there. I mean, unfortunately there are great reputation.
Why do you think they made me advocate? And then somebody reached out on IG to make me an advocate
for a place called Bark. They're known to put cats down to sleep and people. So I said no.
Yeah, yeah, you want to use no kill shelters if you're yeah, no kill those are the only ones
I'll advocate for and everybody knows me out here, you know with the cats and
The landlords adore me because of what we do and how I got so many people involved in how
We helped a lot of the feral's because they're there weren't that many anymore where I was at
Over here. It's taken care of so yeah, and it's mostly the Spanish community that helps
Yeah, I have a big heart and they're very helpful and I got one that she goes around to different places to feed all the cats
You know just and then they have carriers and things and we help each other and people
We give them a number where to call
One of the shelters I advocate for and what they do is they'll come pick the cat up from them and bring it back at two o'clock
And they'll get them fixed
Yeah, that's a great service.
We want to support places like that that are
such that today they go kind of
above and beyond for people
and for the cats and so
you know, support that
and really
just try to put more
of our attention and focus on to
things like that rather than
some of this YouTube drama.
Let me see if we have
Bita trying to come up. Let me see if it's
really her. Okay, we can check
apparently hold on a second
It's me. I just really want to apologize and I really want to say sorry because I really really miss you Marble's magic
and tricks i hope you're having a good life wherever you are because your fucking owner
didn't give a fuck about you he cared about fish tacos and scamming people love you tricks love
you marble love you magic wherever you are i hope you're living a way better life than you did in
that fucking dungeons with this fucking monster fuck you psyche i'm gonna go to police now whore
Okay, um wow see see and I nice that's why I can't be friends with her again
You see with like that kind of like low hurt though, you know, why I'm hurt you I'm hurt you
Yeah, I'd be like that too pissed off because she's hurt. What did I do? I wouldn't I think I think one
Dungeon is something that people are like people are locked into a dungeon and be like, you know locking locking a cat like and never
I don't think those cats are-
We take great care of her cats, and they're happy-
Well, so do I.
So do I.
Yeah.
But I like the way-
That's where I started picking up with how she takes the cats out.
Oh, wait.
We have a double team.
So now we're going to have her little boyfriend come in and yell at us, too.
Let's have a go.
Who's that?
My dick in your mouth, nigga.
Why are you mad?
Why are you kicked there?
I didn't kick her.
She lives on her own.
That's the tricks, man.
Did you ever find her?
No, I never found tricks. No God bless America. What happened to what happened to Ninji?
Well, you tell me what happened in it. Did he died Karen? That's Karen having a ninja Karen. Oh, I don't know about his
Karen hired people
Chatter Karen hired
Try to hire a person trying to grape a chatter
That's true
What are you talking about? What's happened to your cat? He's asked yeah, you tell me
Great
Yeah, you want to see what what she had to say about you you
Fish tank get him off he's a piece of shit
face. Get him off. His mom, a Josephina. You want to see? Wow, Josephina. Yeah, get him off.
Use my clap coin. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, he's just a weirdo. He doesn't have a life like KK said
that he's all over the place and just panel after panel all night long and all day.
You know, and he won't show face and he's supposed to be a streamer.
and then his wife looks like a man oh my god and then he tries to fuck with Brandon and
Brandon didn't even do anything to him you know that's why he runs when Brandon yells
it and he's scared of Brandon have you noticed when Brandon came on a couple of times and
yells practically you know he barely yelled at him and he goes goes running but he did that with Barry
I'll tell you what happened to his dog Karen. He lived a full life. He lived a full life in a home
He wasn't missing. He didn't get eaten by coyotes. He didn't have sleep
He doesn't have cats he fucking babysits cats where people once in a while his buddies alright, so stop with the fucking narrative
All right, don't talk cuz you know what Karen when you were going through shit and people were fucking making out of your dogs
I was there for you. But hey when you're sitting up here when you're sitting up here press that motherfucker
I want to know where marble is
I want to know where magic is.
I want to know what trick says.
All right.
So do not sit here and say you're an animal advocate.
Next to that fucking weirdo.
Then you're meeting yourself.
Look like a piece of shit.
You sit next to pedophiles and people
that are animal abusers.
Good luck.
He's an animal abuser beta. Well, what is she talking about? What animal did you abuse and you're not here in my state?
So I mean I'm here. This is what we take care of what we got here
We can't stop people abusing them. I had a this was four years ago
I went to the bio because they called me and there was a little girl over there screaming with her mom
And there was a lot of people out there and they had two black guys
And they said the dogs in the water, so I took my rescue friend with me and I got in the water to try to take the dog and they, it was a bait dog because they were running some kind of pit bull fight ring or whatever.
And they were trying to drown it because they didn't need it anymore and they cut off its tail in the water.
and we pulled him out of there and I'm all bloody and I tied something around the tail so he wouldn't
bleed so much and my friends were helping me and we rushed him to the vet but you know so I wasn't
worried about those guys I had blood all over my t-shirt and people were screaming saying be careful
that other guys are in water with you because the other one took took off running to the truck to
Inquiring about where his cats are is way less hurtful than him constantly saying that I killed my ex-husband
So for you motherfuckers that say wow wow in the chat
Why don't you fucking ask him to be a better fucking person be more responsible?
Be a good cat owner and don't fucking put false claims on people
It's okay to say that I killed my ex right psyche
But you know what you you heard what I killed my ex
It must be America must be fucking great where I can just get away with murder, right?
You still talk to your ex sometimes.
So listen, magic, marbles, tricks.
I will say this, I hope wherever you are,
you're in a good home, you're being taken care of,
fed the right foods instead of being in the streets
looking for mice and rats to bring in.
And you fucking sit there
and you talked about my whole fucking family.
You put so much anger in me.
And yeah, I'm gonna give it back to you.
Now you're making false claims, I dox you.
I'm gonna show you what really you did, all right?
Well, look up for the shorts.
We'll figure it out today.
I gotta go take care of something really important psyche, so you keep your fucking ratchet nasty fucking mouth about me clothes
Disgusting piece of shit. I killed my husband. Really? Yeah, proof of that. I killed my fucking husband, right?
the thing we both live in California
with your fucking allegation, I'm not next.
Yeah, it's a lot more hurtful
the shit that he said about me,
fucking about my own family
than me saying where the fuck are those cats?
Cause I truly care about those cats.
This man is sitting over here smiling, laughing,
worrying about buttholes, buttholes
instead of his fucking cats.
Fuck you, N-word, there.
Psyche.
and buttholes um yeah you know she didn't kill no husband he went to Iran and I didn't say she killed him I didn't say she killed her husband I was like it was suspicious when she said you'll never figure it out um to gaudy and I have that clip where she says you'll never figure it out and I said why why did she say it like that that sounds kind of suspicious she was probably being sarcastic and you know when people mess with you about something but I know that she and then also she was there when my dog was sick though you know my old dog yeah
She was there, she cared.
She was there too when magic,
but now she's saying, I did something to magic.
I did something to tricks.
I did something to mom.
Yeah, because she cares about animals like me too.
Like I went off at my ex and he had a baseball bat
and I found out later he was hitting them sometimes
and he wasn't taking them out and he was reported too.
It was bad, but I didn't care about the animals
and she does too, because she was there for me
when my dog died and so were the other two people.
Right, well, if you're going to throw it in your face right now and saying that something about, you know, you, I mean, it's like, she just like, you know, she switches up, like, you know, like,
Well, Steve, I'd be hurt too if somebody said I killed somebody that I was with.
I never said she killed her. I never said, I said it sounded suspicious the way she said that one comment. And I, and I was like, I was like, I was like,
She's hurt by it, you know, I'm not hurt by what she says about me. I mean, it's like, you know, it's like,
But you know what, if I could, you guys were friends, you just need to talk and don't listen to those people.
Well, that was over a year ago, and she's the one that turned on me, ended it,
ended up doxing me, you know, with proof, you know, with proof. I mean, it's like, I want to see,
I hope the police comes today. I hope I'm arrested for whatever she's trying to say,
because I will definitely win this.
this case, you know. I can't believe Eldar brought it. That's why I wasn't going to join your panel
yesterday and I said something because I knew he was probably going to start shit or whatever,
you know, just because he's angry at her and he went too far. Well, I mean, it's like, you know,
she's gone too far too, you know, and she didn't hurt anyone. She's not a physical person. She had
feelings like all of us do. She might yell and stuff, but she doesn't go out and hurt people.
And I've never hurt her. Actually, I've made some threats in the past, but she's never made threats.
Well, not yeah, but yeah, no never and she was always there about my dog and cats and we used to send pictures about our pets
She even did the very voiceover on that Pekingese puppy that my sister had and she's she's bigger now
Yeah, and she's still small
And you see, I'm very calm.
She's obviously very triggered about something.
And one reason people get triggered is if they are.
Well, if somebody said I killed a family member or somebody,
I'd be triggered too.
I mean, especially some, Chris, how'd you kill the cat?
No, Kitty died and she was 20 years old.
She's the one that brought it up.
And I can play that clip again.
I can play the clip again, but, you know.
The trip kick made she had no problem with trip kick making the video about it
She has still no problem with the trip. He made a video about it to the drama like that see that's that kind of sexo, too
Yeah, but she liked the video. I mean I saw her you know
She was I think there was laughing emojis at the video or something like that. So she liked the video
I mean she like she likes trip kick, you know
I thought you said they were they did a video of
Eldo no
Yeah
There's a beta, you know, the Black Widow conspiracy where, you know, she's also saying that she's going to like, you know, take everyone's money.
I recorded it, but I wasn't going to play it because of the beta. I didn't even want to watch it.
I just hit the record. It was recording and I heard it was pretty bad, so no, I'm not going to use it.
And so I didn't put it up.
Well, Bad Boy Bree says getting a hitman is not out of the question, so keep on going, he says.
So now he's um, you might want to hit man. Who said that boy breezes posted that yeah
He's gonna get a hit man. He said it's not out of the question. So keep on going he says
He can be funny though sometimes
I just know I love animals and I know Bita does too and we had had good conversations about them, you know, and she loves her cats and takes takes them for walk like I do mine now with my dog, you know, what dog I have one one dog right now and take pictures and videos and stuff on him and they stick right with us they don't need a leash or anything and they come right back inside
And they love my dog and people when they see him at the window, they're like, wow, that's how do you get the cats to get along like that with the dog?
And I said and then when I looked at my window as my pickies was sitting in the middle and the rest of them were
Either both sides of him looking out
Like they were a family. Yeah
And it's like, you know what you're welcome to have whatever
Relationship or you'd like with anybody and it's like it's not my relationship. It's your relationship with that
You know, it's like, but yeah, as for me, it's like, you know, she's going, she's the one going low.
I mean, it's like, because she is very sensitive though, psyche. And you are too, you guys just need to calm down.
Don't let idiots on panel to, you know, like, um, Eldo do that to her.
You know, you guys were friends before and see, that's the thing that messes it up.
And I don't know. I learned my lesson the hard way.
I swear I have to keep my balance like this, you know, sometimes I sway a little bit.
And now number one are my pets, my rescues. So I think about things. I don't do anything stupid
like I did before because they're number one. Because if anything happens to me, what happens
to them? Because my younger siblings said that if something happens to me, they'd only take my dog
You know and it's weird because my brother came over one day and he fell in love with my Russian blue cat and he hates cats and he goes oh what a beautiful cat and she came up to him and and he was patting her he goes oh I love this cat.
Yeah.
You know, and I said, well, you yeah, it's just weird. Yeah, the others hide from people or from him
I was like they can tell when you don't like them though cats and dogs. Oh
Yeah, they can my cats would not be around me sleeping nearby me and
Like they would just sleep with me and they're all quiet. They're so quiet
They only yeah, and my dog only bites when I'm not bites barks when I'm not home and my neighbors
Notice that it's like, you know, they're just like protecting my place. I guess
In the chat they think they say I'm losing it. I just don't know I'm losing it. I'm just I'm pretty calm
Just talking, I don't know, I'm not screaming
and accusing people of killing their animals
or anything like that.
I don't go as low as some of these people, you know?
I would not do that.
Well, except in Sam Man's case,
because I'm going right back.
Grace, self-awareness.
Well, how about, why are you in my chance?
I mean, it's like, how about you disappear?
Whoop.
Bye. Okay. I mean, you could have that talk with with beta and you know, she is very sensitive
That's one thing I found and she did care for you and and that's why she's hurt. So
Somebody come on there to about docs and her. I've been extremely hurt. Yeah
I'm extremely hurt and I never went behind the scenes
giving out her information to anybody and
Saying harass her what she has done to me. And so, you know, obviously
she has some kind of like guilt, or else she can't say sorry.
She has to say she's sorry for what she was like,
you know, brings up my cats and stuff.
I mean, it's pretty interesting.
just uh well she's concerned because like me she also keeps her cats inside i'd sometimes
get mad at people for letting them out look i have the baby kitten here though and we're gonna
get mad at her but she's gonna be bad at over a hundred million people of the country that have
indoor outdoor cats you know cats were not born indoors it's not their natural state i know but
we got to take care of them they they get uh you know everything's happening at any pet especially
when they're out in the wild, they're not used to that.
Anything can happen to them.
So I'd rather keep them safe because they're my babies.
Right, it's like letting your kid out in the middle of the road or whatever and say
But then again, you do eventually let let Lino your you would you eventually let them out
You don't keep you know people locked inside the hat like you know you let your cats
You do what you want walks with your cat and they come with me. Yes, and that's why people take pictures and you know
Just yeah, they do that because I've trained them that way. I would never let them out like that on their own
right well i think like the youngest baby i don't let her out at all yet because
i don't want her running off because she she was was living outside on her own yeah
So until she gets used to being with our walks up, you know, you got to pretty much train them and they'll stick around with you.
Right. Well, I do have like a large, like a large outdoor area that's on the property, you know, so it's like, you know, the cats.
Bill, we had large properties and I was still there. My family was like that with all our pets.
Yeah.
Except for the horses, you know, they were outside. We had two of them.
You know, but yeah, never. I mean, it's just not safe out there, you know, I remember we had one dog that was out one time and he got bit by bat and my family was worried because they, you know, they thought it would get rabies or something.
Right.
You know, and so no, I mean, you got to take care of those babies. I don't let my cats out or.
And it took me a while to find her and it's like, no, I don't I don't let them out at all. It's not safe out there. And you said you have coyotes out there. I wouldn't.
The city, I mean, we shouldn't have coyotes. That's the problem. The problem is there's like a nature and that the animal control will not pick up the coyotes.
They will only if the coyotes injured or if it's near children or something like that.
But that's why I wouldn't let any cat out, especially with coyotes out there. They're they hunt
Yeah, but if I but if I'm gonna be held responsible work for the coyote, then it's like yo
I guess everybody, you know, all the people that have animals outside dogs and the coyotes get dogs cats
They go in backyards. They I mean and so it's like, you know, it's very difficult to you know
You can't predict that kind of thing you all you can do is you know, I'm saying keep him inside
I wouldn't let him out. There's right here. There's any we even won coyote out there
No way would I let any of my pets out there like that, right? Well, you know
There's also there's the quality of life that you know the cats like
go outside, you know, they like to be in the sun sometimes, and just to never be allowed outside.
So she's calling, but I keep them in a dungeon. I keep my cats in a dungeon. A dungeon is locked
up. A dungeon doesn't have a door. I might mind out with me on the walks and also in my porch when
I'm out there with them.
And they're fine they get enough sun and if anything get a category like a type of thing that I had a friend of mine get because they have four cats and they're happy and they'll put them out in the yard in it and they're safe from any dogs or any type of animals get into them.
right. And it's beautiful. And they keep them inside. Hey, little, there you are. She's still trying to get you to the baby. She's there at the baby.
Okay, well, yeah.
But yeah, so yeah, thanks for letting me up. And I'm just gonna ignore the bullshit because everything else is going great for me. And the baby cat is happy. I'm glad I saw her mom outside. I wonder if she would recognize her. But
Yeah, so have a great day, but please just be easy on on be maybe y'all have it
I didn't really go after her that much
I just said here's that here's the proof of what of what um, he was saying and you know
Because I did have receipt and proof because she is lying about it and saying say oh
She gave it to him so he can make me a donation
There's no there's no zeal donation
I received from eldo in the last six months and six months ago wherever she said it was
we were not getting along and so why would she be like oh here you know donate to you know she was
like telling people actively not to and so whatever her bullshit she says you know but that's okay
i'm just gonna leave i'll leave her i'll leave her be whatever i'll let her uh yeah don't let
him up there to talk about whatever yeah well thank you so much Karen yeah okay
We'll see. Yeah, I'm gonna go to Starbucks with a friend. So yeah, now it's top raining. Thank God
Yeah, I don't know I'm kind of like a little bit not feeling a hundred percent today, so
You know, maybe unless someone else comes up and it's gonna play the play the exiting stuff, but you know what?
You know, I just want the truth to be revealed ultimately, and if I'm not afraid of the truth, you know, they say you can't handle the truth, I can handle the truth, I just can't handle all the fucking lies.
And so, if anyone wants to come up, come up, and I'll let you on, but otherwise, enjoy your day.
I'll see you later.
South Bay signal, late night code, everybody wanting pieces of me
Smiles with knives underneath, I learned how the crowd consumes
How applause can become your tomb
So I built my throne from silence first
Watched fake kings rehearse their worst signal
Just like I would do a mercy killing
religious person at all. I don't even believe in God. I don't even believe in God. Just
like I would do a mercy killing because he manifested that, that bullshit in his fucking
life. He got murdered. Yeah, my ex got murdered. I would do a mercy killing.
Sly and ruthless with legs that go all the way to her abdomen.
This bulbous beauty could knock you out with just one bite.
But don't jump to conclusions.
This iconic arachnid is mostly misunderstood.
She's not a bad girl.
She just looks like one.
This is the Black Widow.
Black widows are a type of spider perhaps best known for,
well, you know, sexual cannibalism.
That memorable behavior is where the Black Widow got its name.
She has a sweet side, right?
that it's like the mean side is mean,
cruel, vindictive, and just this stuff,
I can't believe she was saying some of the stuff
she was saying tonight.
Basically, it seemed, I don't know, I'm gonna repeat it,
but basically, you know, she was asked about,
you know, oh, you know, even had a lot of relationships,
like five exes or something, and she's like,
she's like, yeah, and like one of them was murdered,
and,
And she's like, okay, but here's it with me, but you know, it's up to me to force it.
And she's like, what happened?
And she's like, you'll never figure it out.
And it was like, she said it seriously.
And I was like, and I would have been like, yeah, it was a joke.
But then after tonight, she's like, oh, yeah, I call clumsy.
He said he's going to take care of, if anybody bothers me from Texas, he's in that.
I don't know if it's something bad and I was like something like violence or something and it's like
She was referring to Alex and I was like what the hell is going on Dita?
What's what's going on and then I think and then I hear all of a sudden people are telling that this car reverse that you're a part of
Like these people they clip me. That's what they do dog. If you go on YouTube and all this shit
It was paralyzed. I wouldn't want to live if I was paralyzed like the whole body paralyzed
Don't ever say that because my ex used to say that all the fucking time and because he had MS
And he's like if I ever become paralyzed, I am gonna kill myself
But he didn't do that like he was a fucking like talented artist like fucking made like
$30,000 a fucking month
Bringing that same thing up again a bunch
But he didn't because he manifested that that bullshit in his fucking life
He got murdered
Oh, I'll see what you're the guy that was making 30k a month got murdered. Yeah, my ex got murdered and not when I was with him
We're already the worst. How was he doing to make? Yeah, was he running? That's why you got murdered
No, he didn't get murdered for that. He was a captain. He was like a what do you call it? He did like, you know
No, he did contract or he was a captain in her
He was working man
So who murdered like how?
How'd that go about that's something that you guys would never fucking figure out you killed him, huh?
Yeah, what do you think you've black widow? I hate what people do that
They drop a bomb on you like oh, I'm not telling you anymore, but you like told us like a huge thing
Oh, you gotta find the clues man. I'm a cocked. He's
I'll let me in chatting as well. Let me check
See do you want to hurt yourself?
What do you want to hurt yourself?
Do you that's a yes, huh? Don't reflect. Do you do?
Don't reflect. I didn't say yes. Do you want to hurt yourself? Do you want to? All right, that's not a no
Are you okay? I'm gonna call them up. No phone
Say you want to hurt yourself? You got the high res. Oh, what do you do?
Why would I ever want to hurt him or anybody else?
Yeah, that's not your type.
You're not like that at all.
You're still the opposite.
There's been investigations done.
There's been several documentaries.
I'm pretty sure my name is not in any of that.
That's just insanity.
I know, I know, I know.
Does people like to start shit rumors?
Oh shit, I gotta go.
He's getting ready.
Love you.
Thank you for joining them.
Yeah, there's no trash talk, Charisma.
Trash talk.
Like everything that happens on these panels most of the time will be either trash talk real talk people will debate
But if you sit there and you align yourself and you're like I agree with that and you don't stand up for like what is right or wrong
You know it is I think it's criminal
I am being accused of being part of like some really weird shit
Some weird shit and here I see psyche reading this whole thing saying look it these are like the signs of the narcissist and a sociopath and yeah the way he literally said that the way I said my husband was murdered it was so weird and creepy and something
must have happened and I'm hiding like is he fucking insane.
Me and my ex like when this happened to him, we were already divorced for three to almost four fucking years
It was in a different fucking country and this is like the shit like this is what I'm saying trash talk is one thing
Reality is another thing
That's that's you know, there's a big difference between that
I'm now saying somebody murdered their husband murdered somebody else. These are all like, you know allegedly in Minecraft
They're part of the you know some kind of trafficking and this and that that stuff is like allegations
I would really hurt and harm somebody
There's really no way to prove yourself
You know
And it said unless you stand up and be like where's the fucking proof or get a charge for defamation. That's it
If you're gonna say something come with fucking proof always, and I'm really really really disappointed in you Alexander Mayer
Because you haven't cut the crap you still go back and doing the same like bullshit that you always do
Make videos and post people like put people in like some kind of like
Conspiracy now some of them may be like well-deserved, but not everything that you're doing is like facts. They're not
Correct. They're not accurate. You hurt me really really bad
Really really bad like I cried over that and for me crying over that bullshit you best your fucking ass
You're gonna cry 10 times harder. You will I
Would retract that shit and apologize and I would pray to the God that you believe it and ask for forgiveness
That you know what this was wrong of me because it circles around what goes around comes around somebody's gonna hurt you like that
Believe me believe me
I literally, I mean, seriously, that's like another thing.
Oh, P.D. is not outgoing, P.D.
You don't know what I do.
I wake up 5 fucking 30.
Like the latest I wake up is 7 30 in the morning.
Even if I fucking do an all nighter,
I am gonna get up and wing it.
I got shit to do.
I make sure my shit is done.
I do go out. I don't have to tell you every time I go somewhere or do this and this and that, Alec.
If you don't ever go anywhere, okay, all right.
What's it to you what I do? I know a lot of people want me, a lot of people want me, a lot.
I just, I just like, I'm, I forgive people.
Like, you know, I'm really stupid at this.
Like maybe once, even twice or three times,
I gotta just learn to read the fucking signs.
And I don't even know.
I don't know.
We're gonna put you on it.
See, this is another one.
This is where rumors get started, you know?
This is where rumors, like,
and all this shit becomes funny.
This is like somebody like that.
YouTube justice warrior, okay?
Well, why don't you call the police about that?
All right?
Call them and tell them I did that,
and see what you're going to get for false allegations.
Recharge. Imagine trying that hard to get banned,
but coming off as completely cringe.
What do you mean? Who's trying to get banned?
I should learn how to fucking solve a net.
because I no longer can be a gangster.
I'm a retired ex-gangsta.
I'm gonna cry and then they said biscuit.
Again, I'm like, Jesus fucking Christ,
the shit they say about me.
You're sitting there quietly,
snarking and laughing about it.
Would the like J-Dog and Alex are fucking calling me?
Like, I should be serving like 10 life sentences right now,
not on this panel.
And you're sitting there now standing up and saying once, no, that's not true.
Christine, no, she doesn't do that. No, you just feed into it, you love it.
But if somebody says it about you, God fucking for a bet.
Hell to the fucking Christ. Let's get a whole army. Let's get this board together.
Let me get somebody to fucking just like, just battle your own fucking shit.
That's why I'm like I don't want to deal with him unless he's a real man when psyche decides on his own that he's gonna
Be a real individual person. Maybe one day we can be friends when Alex decides what she said about me
Was fucked up wrong
Discriminate all of the above remove it apologize. Maybe I'll have respect for her until then it's okay
I'll leave it up to fucking nature and karma
And anything that I do will always be legally.
Don't worry about that.
Nobody's gonna come and hurt you, Alex, okay?
It's gonna be done legally, always.
Yeah, why not why not praise people or be there for people and lift them up when you're good with them
And they haven't done shit to you until they fuck up with you then you're like all right you give them
I sat there quietly. I ignored it. This is the third or fourth day
It's going on with Alex with psyche is non-stop the shorts the AI music
Be the the pictures like that. He knows he doesn't even I realize like he doesn't even really know me at all
I don't think he's even really seen
Me to an extent to know how to make AI about me. It was really discriminative like I was like
I don't look anything like that. He literally googled Persian woman with big nose and curly hair. I
mean my
Even if I tanned all of my life, I would never get the bronze look the Indian look that that AI picture
Then why are you even doing it when you see that my friendship with you is being like, you know
Spaced and I don't want to be around there. Why are you antagonizing me? Why are you bringing up?
You know Christine why isn't Christine over there in your chat is because me I'm telling Christine don't go over there
You're delusional and fucking paranoid
He went on a round page trying to follow a bunch of people. Yeah, my my thought was yo like he you know
I don't know all of a sudden he's following
That's fresh that's fresh. Oh, I mean, I don't know that's not her behavior. I
We're gonna get Emma for interview for you. So what's fucking Amber HHH HHH HHH did to fucking Alex
I'll make sure it's gonna happen in my stage.
You can do it in your state too.
I don't care dude, I don't even give a shit.
I'm not here to play fucking.
Don't ever come around like,
accusing people of like,
really, really, really, really outrageous behavior.
Okay?
What's up Julia?
Don't.
Especially when I got the chinching and the ding-ding.
Listen, I don't want to take your inheritance that you got.
You bought it from the thrift store?
Well, which one did you want?
I don't want to take your inheritance.
I want you to travel around and enjoy that while you can.
I'm not that kind of a evil bitch.
I've been trying to have a thrifting intermission for you.
But if you had any assets and property sitting solid, like under your fucking name, I'll sweep
that off of your fucking speech right away.
We're fucking the same you know, but like I already know what I'm doing
Why's that?
Isn't your corner lady?
I know your like your stories don't make sense at all ever, but it's cool. Shut up fucking good
blogger
Um, fuck the reason why she should shut their fucking mouth about me is like, um, actually like not a criminal
I like even like a ticket. I paid on time
Um, like all of that. I have no criminal records. I have no restraining order against me. Um,
It's been like January, um, I know yeah, I'm getting into the program to get my master's degree
We're having it
If my name is on the internet for any of you motherfuckers, if you have any property, it's not gonna be good for you
House in California like you beta well my house in California is for Texas because I don't like
I don't talk a stretch what's it protected by by a fucking like law and nobody's gonna fucking like have any case against me
We're training people
What the fuck framing them?
Putting their name out there. I don't know be the listen stop with all the drama for one minute and let's have a
Intense be the listen listen. Let's have a talk. I will tell you that I never had a restraining order against me
If you had one against you
Double down. Let's see what's gonna actually I got I got drunken through some shit through my ex's window
Yeah, I'm restraining it. Oh my gosh. Yeah, I'm not you know, do you have assault charges on her against you?
No, I've never heard a woman like that. That's good
Talking about Arizona
So I can I'll make sure that somebody cannot travel in California either. I did cyborg Betty
I'm trying to make this thrifting
I know
But you want to talk all about drama. I'm just trying to like enter. I'm trying to take a break
I told you I don't need to be a part of a mafia. I would take action legally and
Once somebody has our oil again some like fucking block out and other people
I mean, it's really easy to get a double on
I've never had one. I hate
Where you were I hate I hate all this energy like this. I don't like I was just devastated that I had had a problem and
I even have any of that on my record, right?
Like, I hate all this talk of like,
you putting an arrow on her,
and fucking her making up slander about you.
Like, isn't this all just garbage?
It's not gonna fall.
Like, you think it's gonna fall?
Isn't this, hey, hey,
isn't this just a garbage way to spend your life, right?
Absolutely.
Yeah, so at the very least,
let's just stop talking about this.
Like, who cares?
It was easy for all of us to disappear.
My house was in my mother-in-law's name.
My cars were registered to my wife, my social security cards and driver's licenses were phonies.
I never voted, I never paid taxes. My birth certificate and my arrest sheet.
That's all you'd ever have to know I was alive.
See, the hardest thing for me was leaving the life. I still love the life.
We were treated like movie stars with muscle. We had it all just for the asking our wives mothers kids
Everybody rode along. I had paper bags filled with jewelry stashed in the kitchen
I had a sugar bowl full of coke next to the bed
People call them rats because a rat will do anything to survive isn't that right Mr. Hill?
Objection! Objection system!
But they don't know nothing about being a rat. Mr. Hill you know everything about being a rat. It doesn't matter.
Didn't mean anything when I was broke. I would go out and rob some more if you ran everything
We paid off cops. We paid off lawyers. We paid off judges
Everybody had their hands out. Everything was for the taking
And now it's all over and that's the hardest part
Today everything is different. There's no action. I have to wait around like everyone else
Right after I got here, I ordered some spaghetti with marinara sauce, and I got egg noodles and ketchup
From an average nobody
Get to live the rest of my life like a schnook
Because he manifested that that bullshit in his fucking life
He got murdered. Yeah, my ex got murdered. I would do a mercy killing